<Mod>
  <ID>260dd8f3-537a-4d34-b3d5-956cda71eac9</ID>
  <Name>Cronos WIP</Name>
  <Author>Hobbitdur &amp; Cronos Team</Author>
  <Category>Gameplay</Category>
    <Description>
            &#9658; The most ambitious gameplay mod &#9668;

This mod will be the reference in gameplay. It will offer many option to enjoy the game.
Thus, everyone will find his way of playing: No XP, balanced mod, nightmare mod, ...
It provides also simple change for everyone that just want specific change on their vanilla game.
With this mod you can make the following modification:

    &#9670; General option &#9670;
        &#8226; Language: For the moment only English works, except for gerogero uncensored.

    &#9670; Monster rework (Until Ifrit) &#9670;
        &#8226; MonsterRework: Stat rework (Mathematical improved formula and stat change) + AI rework

    &#9670; Cronos Rework &#9670;
        &#8226; EncountersRework: Change all encounters in the game
        &#8226; FieldRework: Change fields data like dialog, quest, save point position,..
        &#8226; MngrpRework: GF refine abilities
        &#8226; ShopRework: Shop rework
        &#8226; StartData: The data you start with
        &#8226; DrawPoint: The draw point magic/quantity
        &#8226; KernelRework: Change magic/item/weapon/abilities/monster attack/...
        &#8226; WIP: For testers

    &#9670; Game fix &#9670;
        &#8226; BahamutRareItem: Now actually increase the probability of really rare item.
        &#8226; GerogeroUncensoredMenu: Use the japanese version without color change.
        &#8226; GerogeroUncensoredBattle: Use the japanese version without color change.
        &#8226; TrueRandomness: Use a real random generator.
        &#8226; SquallComputeHit: Make squall fail sometimes !

    &#9670; Quality of life &#9670;
        &#8226; DamageCap: All damage can deal up to 65.535 (Eden damage is also cap to 65.535).
        &#8226; NoMagicDepletion: Using magic doesn't decrease your stock.
        &#8226; 255AP: Earn 255 AP after battle.
        &#8226; SaveAnywhere: To be able to save in field. Use at your own risk !

    &#9670; Little gameplay mod &#9670;
        &#8226; NoXP: Don't earn any XP at end of battle.
        &#8226; TripleTryhard: Card values changed for a challenge. => To be tested
        &#8226; QueenForest: Queen of cards and Chocobo forest updated to be more convenient => To be tested

    &#9670; DifficultyBalance &#9670;
        &#8226; LimitbreakNotRefreshable: Make it impossible to refresh to get your limit-break.
        &#8226; NoGfHeal: No free heal on GF on hotel or by walking?
        &#8226; DamageFormulaUpdate: Change damage formula to have a smoother progression. Don't divide magic monster damage by 2.
        &#8226; JunctionRework: Junction value is linked to level or min between the level and the number of magic junctionned.
        &#8226; DrawRework: Change the draw logic(Either draw more than 9 or draw 100)
        &#8226; 255HitCanFail: Make that weapon can fail even at 255%.

    &#9670; Dev setup &#9670;
        &#8226; AddRandomVar: Allow modders to use random numbers in the AI.

    &#9670; Special thanks &#9670;
        &#8226; myst6re for Deling tool and RE work
        &#8226; Nihil for AI, stat, encounter rework
        &#8226; Malekith for stat rework
        &#8226; Unicorngoulash for LimitBreakNotRefreshable
        &#8226; AxlRoses for the awesome preview
        &#8226; Maki for his work on RE
        &#8226; Dulca for TripleTryHard and QueenForest
        &#8226; Dangerous Dom for beta testing

        Join the team or follow the news by clicking on the link ! Help me to continue this work participating in the Patreon page !

        Dev note - This mod use the following cave code:
        0x45B38C, 0x4670DC, 0x462605, 0x4626F9, 0x463090
    </Description>
  <LatestVersion>
    <Link>iroj://Url/https$s3.eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/tsunamods.mods/Hobbitdur/cronos.zip</Link>
    <Version>0.7</Version>
      <ReleaseDate>2025-11-25</ReleaseDate>
    <CompatibleGameVersions>All</CompatibleGameVersions>
    <PreviewImage>https://s3.eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/tsunamods.mods/Hobbitdur/Cronos_Preview.png</PreviewImage>
    <ReleaseNotes>
    &#8226; 0.1
        Adding MaximumDraw, DamageCap, NoMagicDepletion
    &#8226; 0.2
        Adding 255AP, SaveAnywhere, BahamutRareItem, GerogeroUncensored, NoUnequippedOnDream, NoXP
    &#8226; 0.3
        Fixing SaveAnywhere
    &#8226; 0.4:
        Adding DamageFormulaUpdate, LimitbreakNotRefreshable, JunctionDependOfLevel, JunctionDependOfMinLevelQuantity, TrueRandomness, G-Soldier
    &#8226; 0.5:
        Change DamageFormulaUpdate, DrawNotLimited
    &#8226; 0.6:
        Adding AiRework, QueenForest , TripleTryhard, SquallComputeHit, 255HitCanFail, GerogeroUncensoredMenu, GerogeroUncensoredBattle
               DrawPoint, FieldRework, MngrpRework, ShopRework, WIP, MonsterRework/Balanced
        Fixing SaveAnywhere
    &#8226; 0.7:
        Fix worldmap draw by changing SquallComputeHit, fix DrawRework/Draw100, fix encounter in forest
        Remove NoUnequippedOnDream (Creates bug when switching GF).
    </ReleaseNotes>
   <DownloadSize>2110</DownloadSize>
  </LatestVersion>
  <Link>https://discord.gg/A7uFA4WqQY</Link>
  <DonationLink>https://www.patreon.com/c/HobbitMods</DonationLink>
  <Tags>
    <string>cronos</string>
    <string>hard</string>
    <string>mod</string>
    <string>gameplay</string>
    <string>hobbit</string>
    <string>hobbitdur</string>
  </Tags>
</Mod>
